For some time now, I've had a message for my country, South Africa.
I would have loved to share it with them because I had this message last November.
Some areas of South Africa will face drought - the time of rain, it will not rain.
Even if it should rain, it will look like it hasn't rained.
But they should not worry.
I am seeing January, February, March to April - we are praying for rain.
March to April - to recover the city back.
There are some parts of cities like North-East, Limpopo and others.
The rain will fall!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Next meeting, I will have time to share my vision with them.
There are two challenges they have now that will affect the country so badly:
power and drought.
What is the cause of this?
It's unusual - a country the other Africans in the past saw as Heaven on earth.
When there is no power, what else again?
It affects the companies and the foreigners will start leaving
because they cannot work or stay without power.
I saw this and I'm praying over it.
The issue of rain -
this February, March - by April,
you will recover your water back.
Three years ago, I said they should have a dam.
It is part of the prophecy that South Africa should prepare to have a dam.
But I think they took it for granted.
Thank you very much.
TT: Mel Flowers 22/04/2019